Preliminary Inventory to the George S. Reppas Papers, 1966-1982
Hoover Institution Archives
- Loan contract papers between AGM and Morgan Guaranty Bank. Includes: (Folder Folder 2)
  - Option agreement and escrow agreement between Arthur D. Little, Morgan, and AGM
  - Consulting advisory agreement between Arthur D. Little and Viande
  - Letter from Resampa as a representative of SOMADELVA to Potamianos urging the starting of activities
  - Statuts of SOMADELVA
  - Balance sheet of AGM as of July 31, 1969
- Prison diaries, typed and bound. Vol 2, Part 1 and 2 (Box 112)
- Album photo from Madagascar: prison, escape, construction, family...
- Several maps of Madagascar, including the property in Morondava
- Original prison diaries
- Prison diaries, typed and bound. Volume 2, Part 1 & 2 (Box 113)
- Several tapes of speeches
- Tapes of speeches (Box 114 to 116)
- Tapes of speeches (Box 117)
- Fiche on each character and individual in the story
- Copy of strange letter from FAKRA (Box 118)
- Suggestion de compromis entre AGM & Etat Malagasy
- Cahier des charges sell off of abattoir by Malagasy Government
- Societe AGM proposal to the Malagasy State on cattle national policy, March 7, 1974
- Several letter on bankruptcy
- Letters to potential leases of the abattoir: Auckland, New Zealand
- Several copies of typed and handwritten letters, receipts, invoices... in prison
- Folder of Mike Reppas' letters
- Folder of several correspondence of AGM, Reppas and local management
- Vasiliky's letters and responses obtained
- Accounting and invoices in prison (Box 119)
- Old Mad. research data
- Correspondence with the State Department for updated info about characters
- Plot summaries: 1st attempts for book
- Misc. correspondence (Rabenjamina...)
- Memo: background of principal individual shareholders and creditors of AGM
- Several letters and correspondence for Newsweek and copy Newsweek magazine
- Articles in the San Francisco Chronicle
- Letters of support from various people
- Copy of 3 letters from Rouleau: Refusing AGM access to Tsiranana; Instructing policy to get land back from AGM; requesting meeting between AGM & SOBERI
- Report on 1st appearance with JDI
- Court decision for bankruptcy after trial
- Study of the viability of a beef slaughter and ranching operation. Submitted to the Malagasy Government by Girton and Proops, Swift Co. (Oct 26, 1971)
- Reppas letter inviting TA and creditors for a meeting for a study of the AGM situation and financing.
- Extrait minute cour de cassation. Court decision.
- Statement of conclusion between Malagasy Gov., Swift, Morgan, Arthur D. Little and SOBERI stopping financing of AGM.
- Presentation of the abattoir to potential buyers by Syndic.
- Swift interactions with AGM: Board position, Management contract, resignation, report study.
- Various articles in US magazines and newspapers on Reppas and Madagascar, and following Ratsimandrava assassination. (Box 120)
- Madagascar photos (1975)
- Several copies and articles in Madagascar Matin on AGM and Ratsimandrava assassination
- Copy of cast of character in the story
- Madagascar photo of 1975
- Reppas' escape in Bay Area newspapers
- Articles on Madagascar political background. Includes:
  - Ambassador Marshall article in San Francisco Chronicle, April 14, 1981
  - Article on recall of Marshall: The egg on uncle Sam's face, 1971
  - Article on Indian Ocean importance by Marshall, June 3, 1981